<content>
    <title>Goo Goo Grapplers Press Kit</title>
    <studio>A Game by Both Good</studio>
    <meta-description></meta-description>

    <description>Goo Goo Grapplers is 1v1 Couch battle arena where you compete with your twin to see who is truly 
        the better baby. Gather “Toy Parts” in exchange for powerful new abilities and upgrades that you can 
        mix and match however you see fit. Shoot some milk, swing a rattle, and toot your way to victory as you lead an army of imaginary friends to take down your siblings pillow fort in this whacky little 
        world.</description>

     <history>From the beginning Goo Goo Grapplers had the goal to bring together elements from two very 
         different places- Platform fighters and MOBAs. In 2023 the first prototype was born, manifesting as 
         something between a tower defense and a fighting game. And while fun, like many prototypes it 
         wasn’t ready to be developed further, and the idea was put to rest. However, after a year more of 
         experience working on various games and gradually getting a small team together, Goo Goo 
         Grapplers awoke from its nap. In it’s new form GGG takes a different approach, bringing together the 
         gameplay, flow and strategy of a MOBA and the accessible, goofy couch fun of a platform fighter. 
         Committed to its development and release, “Both Good” was formed in 2024. The new studio’s aim 
         was not only set on completing and releasing GGG, but also on beginning the early stages of future 
         IPs that are yet to be revealed.</history>

    <!-- List all features in individual feature tags. They'll be turned into bullet points on the front end. -->

     <feature>Same-screen local multiplayer with dynamic split screen</feature>
     <feature>Dozens of unique ability and upgrade combinations</feature>
     <feature>Multiple Map layouts that reward different strategies</feature>
    <feature>An exciting original soundtrack</feature>
    <feature>Cute and colorful pixel art mixed with dynamic lighting and shader effects</feature>
    <feature>Powerful special abilities</feature>

    <!-- Just the end of a given YouTube link, after watch?v=. One per element. -->

     <video>z69Z_Hpk08U</video>

     <!-- The file name of whichever image you want shown in the "imgAndVid" folder! -->

     <images>slideshow1_image1.jpg</images>
     <images>slideshow1_image2.png</images>
     <images>slideshow1_image2.png</images>

     <!-- The file name of whichever logo you want shown in the "imgAndVid" folder! -->

     <logo_and_icon>BothGood_Logo_Web.png</logo_and_icon>
     <logo_and_icon>GGG_Logo_Web.png</logo_and_icon>

    <!-- Selected articles to come! -->

    <monetization>Both Good allows for the contents of Goo Goo Grapplers to be
        published through video broadcasting services for any commercial or
        non-commercial purposes. Monetization of videos created containing
        assets from Goo Goo Grapplers is legally & explicitly allowed
        by Both Good. This permission can be found in writing at
        https://www.googoograpplers.com/GGG_presskit/presskit.</monetization>

    <!-- Links have "link_text," which is what links will embed into, and "link," which is the actual link -->
    <!-- Keep them in this relative order, just copy + paste where needed -->

    <link>https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=LQcMOI8dMas</link>
    <link_text>Links go here.</link_text>

    <about>Founded in 2024 Both Good is an independent game studio located in Brooklyn, NY. We believe in 
        the importance of “play” and games bringing people together. We design games that are friendly 
        and inviting, but with gameplay that can be taken seriously. Our team is dedicated to creating games 
        that we ourselves want to play, and think are worth sharing.</about>

    <credit-name>Luca Civita</credit-name>
    <credit-subtitle>Lead Developer, Programmer, Artist, Co-founder</credit-subtitle>
    <credit-name>Justin Cook</credit-name>
    <credit-subtitle>Game Designer, Operations, Co-founder</credit-subtitle>
    <credit-name>Jason Li</credit-name>
    <credit-subtitle>Production &amp; Planning, Technical Direction</credit-subtitle>
    <credit-name>Jay Tobin</credit-name>
    <credit-subtitle>Audio Design, Composer</credit-subtitle>
    <credit-name>Jay Tobin</credit-name>
    <credit-subtitle>Audio Design, Composer, SEO</credit-subtitle>
    <credit-name>Ally Luo</credit-name>
    <credit-subtitle>Web Developer</credit-subtitle>
    <credit-name>Zachary Mezzo</credit-name>
    <credit-subtitle>Composer</credit-subtitle>
    <credit-name>Sanjay Henry</credit-name>
    <credit-subtitle>Composer</credit-subtitle>
    
    <!--<credit-link>https://splatoonwiki.org/wiki/Big_Man</credit-link>-->

   <contact>Business inqueries email:</contact>
   <contact>BothGood@bothgood.games</contact>
   <contact>Press inqueries email:</contact>
   <contact>contact@googoograpplers.com</contact>
   <!-- <contact>Website:</contact>-->

 <site-title>Goo Goo Grapplers</site-title>
 <site-link>https://www.googoograpplers.com/</site-link>


</content>